#### Contact

8379884496 (Mobile) iamsaib97@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/saikumar-bolamwar-33a2801a2 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Security

Malware Analysis
Incident Response

### Languages

English, Hindi, Marathi, Telugu (Full Professional)

# Saikumar Bolamwar

Cyber Security Engineer

Nagpur, Maharashtra, India

## Summary

An enthusiastic cyber security analyst with 1.7 yrs of hands on experience on various EDR tools. Currently working in TCS wherein I have the architectural knowledge of EDR tools implementation, policies creation, team handling and setting up the process. Young and energetic to learn the technologies and have passion in working as a cyber security engineer.

# Experience

Tata Consultancy Services Cyber Security Analyst August 2021 - Present (2 years) Nagpur, Maharashtra, India

CCIT-Keeping Pace With Technology Developer December 2019 - December 2019 (1 month) Amravati

## Education

Government college of Engineering, Chandrapur Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science & Engineering · (2017 - 2021)

Gurunanak Science College, Ballarpur Higher Secondary Education

Karmveer Vidyalaya yenbodi Secondary Education